export const humorData = [
  {
    question: "The fact that I was born without my permission annoys me.",
    answer: "That push! Push! shows I was forced to be here.",
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "I have stopped visiting people's houses.",
    answer: 'Imagine a child wanted to stab my eye and the mother said "don\'t stop him, he will cry."',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "She reported to the family that her husband is not good in bed.",
    answer: 'Her younger sister shouted "It\'s a lie."',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "Tatto look good when you have money.",
    answer: 'If you are broke you begin to look dangerous',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "Imagine crying at a burial",
    answer: 'Then you check your pocket and don\'t find your phone.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "I bumped into a blind man he said watch where your going.",
    answer: 'So I pointed him towards the road.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "If she caught you cheating she really never loved you.",
    answer: 'Because love is supposed to be blind.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "How do astrology girls get cheated on ?.",
    answer: 'Did you not read the SIGNS ?.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "Golf people destroying millions of acres of forest.",
    answer: 'Just to play the laziest sport ever created.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "If she wants something that will last forever on valentines day.",
    answer: 'Give her nothing because nothing lasts forever.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "God making a world where you don\'t need a Degree to be a business owner.",
    answer: 'But you need a Degree to work for a business owner.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "You need at least 1 witness to prove a murder.",
    answer: 'And a minimum of 2 witnessess to register marriage. It clarifies which one is more dangerous.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "If we removed all laws.",
    answer: 'The crime rate would be zero.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "Being in a relationship is about solving problems together.",
    answer: 'Problems you wouldn\'t have if you were single.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "Who knew you could learn so much from YouTube.",
    answer: 'Anyone want surgery this weekend ? I\'m free.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "Most ladies claim to love money more than sex.",
    answer: 'Suprisingly they get pregnant instead of getting rich.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "I prank my girlfriend yesterday, I said I saw you kissing another guy.",
    answer: 'She apologized.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "If you have any problem, post it on your whatsapp status.",
    answer: 'It will disappear after 24 hrs.',
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "She posted 'no one can take what God given to me'.",
    answer: "And I commented 'where is your virginity ?' She blocked me.",
    type: "dark"
  },
  {
    question: "Donate 1 kidney and you are a Hero.",
    answer: "Donate 10 you are under Investigation.",
    type: "dark"
  },



  {
      question: "What do you call a bear with no teeth?",
      answer: "A gummy bear.",
      type: "simple"
    },
    {
      question: "Why couldn’t the leopard play hide and seek?",
      answer: "Because he was always spotted.",
      type: "simple"
    },

    
  {
    question: "What’s the best thing about Switzerland?",
    answer: "I don’t know, but the flag is a big plus",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "I invented a new word!",
    answer: "Plagiarism!",
    type: "simple"
	
  },
  {
    question: "Did you hear about the mathematician who’s afraid of negative numbers?",
    answer: "He’ll stop at nothing to avoid them.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why do we tell actors to “break a leg?”",
    answer: "Because every play has a cast.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Helvetica and Times New Roman walk into a bar.",
    answer: "“Get out of here!” shouts the bartender. “We don’t serve your type.”",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Yesterday I saw a guy spill all his Scrabble letters on the road. I asked him, “What’s the word on the street?”",
    answer: "Once my dog ate all the Scrabble tiles. For days he kept leaving little messages around the house. Don’t miss these hilarious egg puns that will absolutely crack you up.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Knock! Knock!\nWho is there?\n Control Freak.\nCon…",
    answer: "OK, now you say, “Control Freak who?”",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Hear about the new restaurant called Karma?",
    answer: "There’s no menu: You get what you deserve",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "A woman in labor suddenly shouted, “Shouldn’t! Wouldn’t! Couldn’t! Didn’t! Can’t!”",
    answer: "“Don’t worry,” said the doc. “Those are just contractions.”",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "A bear walks into a bar and says, “Give me a whiskey and … cola.”",
    answer: "“Why the big pause?” asks the bartender. The bear shrugged. “I’m not sure; I was born with them.”",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Did you hear about the actor who fell through the floorboards?",
    answer: "He was just going through a stage.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Did you hear about the claustrophobic astronaut?",
    answer: "He just needed a little space.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why don’t scientists trust atoms?",
    answer: "Because they make up everything.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why did the chicken go to the séance?",
    answer: "To get to the other side.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Where are average things manufactured?",
    answer: "The satisfactory.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "How do you drown a hipster?",
    answer: "Throw him in the mainstream.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What sits at the bottom of the sea and twitches?",
    answer: "A nervous wreck.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What does a nosy pepper do? ",
    answer: "Gets jalapeño business!",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "How does Moses make tea?",
    answer: "He brews.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why can’t you explain puns to kleptomaniacs?",
    answer: "They always take things literally.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "How do you keep a bagel from getting away?",
    answer: "Put lox on it.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "A man tells his doctor, “Doc, help me. I’m addicted to Twitter!”",
    answer: "The doctor replies, “Sorry, I don’t follow you …”",
    type: "simple"

  },
  {
    question: "What kind of exercise do lazy people do?",
    answer: "Diddly-squats.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why don’t Calculus majors throw house parties?",
    answer: "Because you should never drink and derive.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What do you call a parade of rabbits hopping backwards?",
    answer: "A receding hare-line.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What does Charles Dickens keep in his spice rack?",
    answer: "The best of thymes, the worst of thymes.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What’s the different between a cat and a comma?",
    answer: "A cat has claws at the end of paws; ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why should the number 288 never be mentioned?",
    answer: "It’s two gross.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What did the Tin Man say when he got run over by a steamroller?",
    answer: "“Curses! Foil again!”",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What did the bald man exclaim when he received a comb for a present?",
    answer: "Thanks— I’ll never part with it!",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What did the Buddhist say to the hot dog vendor?",
    answer: "Make me one with everything.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What did the left eye say to the right eye?",
    answer: "Between you and me, something smells.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What do you call a fake noodle?",
    answer: "An impasta.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "How do you make a tissue dance?",
    answer: "Put a little boogie in it.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What did the 0 say to the 8?",
    answer: "Nice belt!",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What do you call a pony with a cough?",
    answer: "A little horse.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What did one hat say to the other?",
    answer: "You wait here. I’ll go on a head. If you loved this, you’ll get a kick out of these dog puns.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What do you call a magic dog?",
    answer: "A labracadabrador.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What did the shark say when he ate the clownfish?",
    answer: "This tastes a little funny.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What’s orange and sounds like a carrot?",
    answer: "A parrot.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why can’t you hear a pterodactyl go to the bathroom?",
    answer: "Because the “P” is silent.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What do you call a woman with one leg?",
    answer: "Eileen.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What did the pirate say when he turned 80?",
    answer: "Aye matey.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why did the frog take the bus to work today?",
    answer: "His car got toad away.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What did the buffalo say when his son left for college?",
    answer: "Bison.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What is an astronaut’s favorite part on a computer?",
    answer: "The space bar.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why did the yogurt go to the art exhibition?",
    answer: "Because it was cultured.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What do you call an apology written in dots and dashes?  ",
    answer: "Re-Morse code.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why did the hipster burn his mouth? ",
    answer: " He drank the coffee before it was cool. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Once my dog ate all the Scrabble tiles. ",
    answer: " He kept leaving little messages around the house. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " I told my wife she was drawing her eyebrows too high. ",
    answer: "She looked at me surprised.  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Did you hear about the two people who stole a calendar? ",
    answer: "  They each got six months.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " What’s Forest Gump’s password? ",
    answer: " 1Forest1. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " How do poets say hello? ",
    answer: "Hey, haven’t we metaphor?  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "  Where does Batman go to the bathroom?",
    answer: " The batroom. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why did the Oreo go to the dentist? ",
    answer: " Because he lost his filling. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " What do you get from a pampered cow? ",
    answer: " Spoiled milk. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why is it annoying to eat next to basketball players? ",
    answer: " They dribble all the time. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " What breed of dog can jump higher than buildings? ",
    answer: " Any dog, because buildings can’t jump. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "  How many times can you subtract 10 from 100?",
    answer: " Once. The next time you would be subtracting 10 from 90. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why did the M&M go to school?  ",
    answer: " It wanted to be a Smartie. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why do bees have sticky hair?  ",
    answer: "  Because they use honeycombs.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "  How does a rabbi make his coffee?",
    answer: "  Hebrews it.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " I got my daughter a fridge for her birthday. ",
    answer: " I can’t wait to see her face light up when she opens it. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " I poured root beer in a square glass. ",
    answer: " I poured root beer in a square glass. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why aren’t koalas actual bears? ",
    answer: " Now I just have beer.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Rest in peace to boiling water. ",
    answer: "You will be mist.  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " What do you call a rooster staring at a pile of lettuce? ",
    answer: "A chicken sees a salad.  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why did the nurse need a red pen at work? ",
    answer: " In case she needed to draw blood. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "  How do you throw a space party?",
    answer: " You planet. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " The numbers 19 and 20 got into a fight ",
    answer: "21.  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why did it get so hot in the baseball stadium after the game? ",
    answer: " All of the fans left. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " What do you call a train carrying bubblegum? ",
    answer: "A chew-chew train.  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why did the math textbook visit the guidance counselor? ",
    answer: " It needed help figuring out its problems. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why can’t male ants sink?  ",
    answer: "They’re buoy-ant.  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Want to hear a construction joke? ",
    answer: "Oh never mind, I’m still working on that one.  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Talk is cheap?  ",
    answer: " Have you ever talked to a lawyer? ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why did the gym close down? ",
    answer: " It just didn’t work out! ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Two artists had an art contest.  ",
    answer: " It ended in a draw! ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "I tried to sue the airport for misplacing my luggage. ",
    answer: " I lost my case. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " I have a fear of speed bumps. ",
    answer: " But I am slowly getting over it. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Where do you find a cow with no legs? ",
    answer: "Right where you left it.  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " What did one traffic light say to the other?",
    answer: "  Stop looking! I’m changing!",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " What type of sandals do frogs wear? ",
    answer: "Open-toad!  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why was six afraid of seven? ",
    answer: "Because seven ate nine.  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "What do you call a boomerang that doesn’t come back?    ",
    answer: " A stick! ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "  What starts with E, ends with E, and has only 1 letter in it?",
    answer: " Envelope. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why doesn’t the sun go to college?  ",
    answer: " Because it has a million degrees! ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " How do you count cows? ",
    answer: " With a cowculator. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why are skeletons so calm? ",
    answer: " Because nothing gets under their skin. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why is England the wettest country? ",
    answer: " Because so many kings and queens have been reigning there. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Did you hear about the kidnapping at school? ",
    answer: " It’s okay. He woke up. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " What are shark’s two most favorite words? ",
    answer: "Man overboard!  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Can February march? ",
    answer: "  No, but April may.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Where does the sheep get his hair cut? ",
    answer: " The baa baa shop! ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "Why are ghosts such bad liars?  ",
    answer: "  Because they are easy to see through.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why does Humpty Dumpty love autumn? ",
    answer: " Because Humpty Dumpty had a great fall. ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: "  Where do fish sleep?",
    answer: "  In the riverbed.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " How do trees get online? ",
    answer: "They just log on!  ",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " What do you call a bear with no teeth? ",
    answer: "  A gummy bear.",
    type: "simple"
  },
  {
    question: " Why couldn’t the leopard play hide and seek? ",
    answer: " Because he was always spotted ",
    type: "simple"
  }


  ];